

Muhammad Sajjad Rasool

Quality Assurance Executive at Abtach Ltd

Muhammad Sajjad Rasool, a Karachi-based professional with a BS degree from FUUAST Gulshan, excels in English and Urdu language expertise. Currently contributing skills and knowledge to Abtach Ltd, he brings a strong foundation in both languages to enhance communication and content creation.

Strengths & Skills

✓ Computer experience.

✓ Social Media Marketing

✓ TUTOR

✓ Teaching

- ✓ Problem Solving
- ✓ Teamwork
- ✓ Call Center Agent
- ✓ Multitasking
- ✓ Computer skills
- ✓ MS Office

Academics

BS Chemistry / Federal Urdu University of Arts, Sciences and Technology / 3.6 CGPA

FSc / Govt. Higher Secondary School Khan bela / 67%

Matric / Govt. Higher Secondary School Khan

2022

2018

Bela / 76%

2016

Jun 2023 - Jan 2024

Languages • Urdu - Native

- Saraiki Native
- English Medium
- Spanish Beginner

Experience Less than 1 Year

ABTACH Quality Assurance Officer / QA Officer

Projects

Chemistry Expo 2022

🔯 Hobbies

- Music
- Bike riding
- Book reading
- Social media

Work History

ABTACH Jun 2023 - Jan 2024 (7 months)

7 months

Quality Assurance Officer / QA Officer

Karachi, Pakistan



Chemistry Expo 2022 Oct 2022 - Nov 2022 (1 month)

Company: / FUUAST Gulshan-Iqbal, Karachi

Worked on given Topic "Replacement of Conventional Energy by Solar Energy"

software house

Industries

Contact Info

☑ Sajjadr742@gmail.com

♠ Block L, North Nazimabad

Karachi Central Karachi, Pakistan

Awards

http://cvbuilder2023.000webhostapp.com

□ 03142834340

Functional Areas

• Food and Lifestyle Seminar | 2022

- Quality Assurance (QA)
- Quality Control
- Telecommunication
- Education / Teaching